お友達は？
Pouf!
あれが　そうだ。 どうやって見つけたんだい？
If you'd approached him with the intent to kill, he would have immediately attacked Komugi.
教えるわけねえだろ　ボケ。 ふん。
That was a risk I didn't want to take.
その木陰にいる君。
Your words baffle me.
君の能力かい？ 「円」を使ってるわけでもねえのに 化け物か　てめぇ。
Isn't he sitting there because
he wants to help that girl?
フフフ…。 とっても楽しいバトルを 終えたばかりでさ。
You almost make it sound like
he means to harm her. Why?
僕　今　感度ビンビンなんだよね。
It's none of your business.
この猛りを静めるために 見ず知らずの人間なら
Shut up.
クソっ。 出といで。
Once I'm charged up, I'm going back to Gon.
いいえ　完璧だったわ。 こいつの感覚が 半端ねえだけだ。
Pouf is outside the barrier, so it's very likely the big guy was taken out.
こいつは　団員ナンバー４ つまり　てめぇの抜け番だ。
Review the situation, then you and Knuckle decide what
to do, and whether to retreat. Wh-What about you guys?
名前は　カルト どうやったかは言えない。 でも　確かに僕の能力で見つけた。
Once Gon is in that state, he won't budge.
そう…。
At worst, he'll trade his life for Pitou's.
君も　うまそうだ。
I'm kidding!
気ぃつけろ。 あいつ　何でもいけるから。
It'll be fine. I've always got the magic word, "Kite"!
ヒソカ　必ず成功させろよ。
I have it under control.
君達　くどいね。
Really?
させるさ　僕のためにね。
Then why did you
本気で団長と戦う気？ もちろん　マチは　僕とクロロ どっちに生き残ってほしい？
look so sad back there?
愚問ね　あんたの仕事が終わったら すぐ　死んでいいわよ。
You're sure, then?
もし　僕がクロロを殺したら？
You can't talk... And you don't want to, anyway.
あり得ないわね でも　答えてあげる。 どこまでも追いかけて あんたを殺す。
Then I can't ask, and I don't want to!
それ　いいね。
It's none of your business.
俺達の狙いは ゲンスルー組が独占している 「大天使の息吹」。
Shut up?
ゲンスルー組の３人の誰かに 大ダメージを与える可能性は高い。
Downwind, huh?
奴らが　１枚でも 「大天使の息吹」を使えば
Am I interrupting something?
俺達の「引き換え券」が 「大天使の息吹」に変わる。 そうなれば…。
Pitou, I'll let you handle this, then.
残るのは 「奇運アレキサンドライト」のみ！
Don't move.
それも　俺達が ３週間　時間を稼げば
Stay right there.
ゴン達との取引で手に入る。
You can use your wing scales to control others, right?
うむ　よし　時間だ そろそろ行くぞ。
Don't take a single step.
さすがに　意見が分かれてな。
You want me to stand here and do nothing? For that woman's sake?
まだ　話し合いの最中だった。
For the King's sake!
だが　ようやく結論が出た。 ほう。
Do as he says...
「レヴィ」オン！
What happened?
「アカンパニー」オン！ アントキバへ！ あっ！ ブック。
Your expression has changed...
カード確認だ。 ブック！ 大丈夫だ　奪われたのは フリーのクズカードだ。
What happened while I was trapped?
これで決定だな。 奪って　やっちまおう。 手ごわいぞ。 えっ？
I promise that I shall not move from this spot.
何があったか知らんがな
In return, I want you to tell me
あれは　覚悟を決めた者の顔。
everything that has happened thus far.
「アカンパニー」６枚 「リターン」２４枚 「キャッスルゲート」９枚 「マグネティックフォース」２枚。 これで　金は全部使った。
If I ask where the King is, he'll
get suspicious and silence us.
ＯＫ　次は３日後だ それまで　また　金をためて
Drop me hints while you explain what's happened.
必要カードを集めてくれ。 了解。
Be careful to make it sound quite natural.
奴ら　追って来ると思うか？ まず　あるまい。
If you fail, we will see bloodshed.
これで　「アカンパニー」は　俺達のほうが ゲンスルーの倍近く所有している。
That's all there is to it.
見せてやる　ゲンスルー シングルハンターの戦い方をな
It's time. Adding interest.
あっ！　「凝」！ 遅い！　握られたと 頭で自覚してからじゃなく
I could feel myself controlling the explosion.
皮膚で感じた瞬間に！ オス！　ぬお！
If I try it once more, I'll have it mastered.
遅い！ オス！
I need rage...
まだまだ遅い！ オス！
I must build up my rage before
I forget how it felt!
よし　１０分休憩 次は　放出系の修行よ。 オス！
That's the second time you've
made a fool out of me!
はぁ。
Scum! Trash!
スタミナは 順調について来てる でも　あと２週間ほどの修行じゃ 防御に費やすだけで精いっぱい
Piece of crap!
戦うためには もう一つ武器がいる 放出系修行レベル２　浮き手！
Stay calm, and let rage consume me...
この状態から　体は全く動かさず オーラの放出のみで…。
Create and destroy at the same time. Manifested through this body!
…と　まぁ　最低このくらい 体が浮き上がって合格。
Or what his current predicament was.
よし！
Rage...
よっ。
Rage is not intended to be scattered.
うん！
It's meant to be focused on a target!
うっ　うぅ…。 ハッ！
I will destroy you!
当然よ　ホントは レベル５の修行だもの。
Okay! Okay! It's a fake, okay!
５!?　いいのかよ いきなり　レベル上げて。
Keep it up...
まぁ　賭けだわさ。
Make me madder!
身につけなきゃ ３週間は　まるっきり無駄になる。
Come on!
直撃すれば　相手の体が
It's time.
数メートル　すっ飛ぶぐらいの 威力の放出系攻撃
Adding interest.
最低でも　そのぐらいでなきゃ 武器としては使えないわさ。
APR's interest is calculated
それがレベル５か…。
assuming that aura consumption will
continue to rise at the current rate.
でも　それをクリアしたとしても 相手を飛ばす程度じゃ 必殺の武器には　ならないな。 戦術の幅が少し広がる程度だと 解釈してちょうだい。 で　あんたの作戦のほうは？
Even if Youpi were to reduce his
aura usage to a bare minimum, in another three minutes and fifty seconds, he would reach the point at which
he would be unable to use Nen.
その前に　ビスケの能力 教えてくれる？ 分かってたほうが 立てやすいんだけど。
Ten left.
私の能力　紹介するわ。
My back's against the wall...
「マジカルエステ」の クッキィちゃん。
Looks like he's saving me for last.
彼女の　さまざまなマッサージは 至福の愛撫。 余分な脂肪を燃焼させ 身も心も楽園へ　いざなう。
In that case, I'll keep fighting as long as I can!
オーラを 特別なローションに変化させ お肌に塗れば 若返り美肌の効果！
Morel had deployed all of his puppets
close enough for Youpi to see
指圧マッサージは 体の内から美しく 便秘　肩こり　冷え性などの悩みを スッキリ解消！ それだけ？ とんでもない！ 整体マッサージ　瞑想マッサージ
so that he'd be able to monitor Youpi's movements, but also because he no longer had the
strength to move his puppets around.
ロールマッサージ まだまだ　あるわさ！
If he lost his focus, the puppets would
return to smoke and dissipate.
アホか　てめぇは！ 全く使えねえじゃねぇかよ！
It shouldn't be much longer...
何言ってんのよ　こんな便利な能力 他にないってのよさ！
He has to run out of Nen at some point. But...
これだから　ババアの考えることは！ フッ！
But damn...
ハッ！
My body and soul...
あっ！
At this point, Morel could not
even will himself to stand.
待て　こら！
He had literally reached his limit
even before Youpi went bankrupt.
今も　完全に やる気で狙いやがって。 問題は　そこじゃねえ。
Zero left...
「アカンパニー」や 「マグネティックフォース」を使って 飛んで来たなら　すぐ分かるが そうじゃねえし。
I have something to say to you.
奴らは　ヒットアンドアウェ－で 攻撃後　すぐに逃げ
Now that Youpi had learned
俺達も　すぐ別の場所へ 移動してるが それも　あっという間にバレる。
how to store his rage elsewhere,
his head was much clearer.
発信機や尾行 スペルの類いでないとすると レーダー機能に 似た能力を持つ奴が
You look like a little fly that's about to die.
仲間の中にいるとしか 考えられない。
And yet...
それじゃ　防ぎようがないぜ？ どうする？
That's what makes you guys amazing.
少し　乱暴なてを使うか。
During the battle, Youpi had
evolved at an alarming rate, increasing the gap between
the Hunters and himself.
おっ！ 「アカンパニー」１枚ゲット。 ランクＣのカード あったら　もらっとけよ。
Yet he had nothing but praise for the defeated.
うぅ…。 「スティール」を　はめまして。
Given Morel's initial impression of Youpi, this must have been the last thing he
expected Youpi to say in this situation.
会ってねえな。 じゃ　一応　シロだ。 ひぃ！
But Morel could honestly accept
that this was Youpi's true nature.
おい　ボマーって知ってるか？
I'm not sure how to say this...
はい　噂は…。 俺達が　そうだ。 ひぃ！
But because you've impressed me, I have to be sure to kill you.
もう　いつでもどこでも お前を殺せる。
This is game over.
死にたくなければ これから言うカードを持って来い。
Well, I'll end this with one blow.
おっ　「アカンパニー」 またまたゲット。
I don't think I even mind letting him kill me now.
それでは　「スティール」を セットしまして。
Bye.
ヤバい… 奴ら 何てことを考えてやがる！
He disappeared?
奴ら スペルカードの店を張ってるんだ。
It wasn't teleportation?
そして　カードを買って 出て来たプレ－ヤーを 手当たり次第　攻撃してる。
The moment I was about to cut through him, he disappeared.
奴らは　俺の存在に気づいたんだ。
I thought that one of them had the
ability to use teleportation...
新たな仲間が　ツェズゲラ組の カード供給係をしてることにな。
But when he disappeared,
I didn't see anyone else.
店に入ったプレーヤー全員の バインダーを調べて
And I struck before he disappeared, so if
he teleported, I shouldn't have drawn blood.
あんた達と 会ったことがあるプレーヤーは
But I was able to cut him.
問答無用で処分する。
Yet I can no longer see him.
その際に　カードも奪ってる。
Does that mean he only turned invisible?
主な狙いは　「アカンパニー」と 「マグネティックフォース」だろう。
An ability to become transparent?
カードの収集を強いる徹底ぶりだ。
Which means one of the others
容疑者を減らし　カードを奪い こちらのカード供給源も断つ。
must be able to make himself
and the rest invisible.
一石三鳥の作戦だぜ。 分かった　奴らの動向は こちらで追跡する。
And right before I connected, he tried
to save the guy with the sunglasses.
お前は その場を離れて待機してくれ。
But I left a deep wound.
よし　次はカードの確認だ。
The blood... Youpi can follow the blood!
３人で合計　「アカンパニー」１６枚 「マグネティックフォース」２枚。
We may be invisible, but the
blood is leaving a trail.
結構　増えてるな。 今のペースで集められると あと　４５日で追いつかれる。
If he swings that blade again,
I'll have to get away by myself.
だが　それも　予想の範ちゅう。
I'm running out of breath...
奴らは　自ら　カードが集まるまで 動かないと言ってるも同然だ。
Damn it!
うぅ…。
Knuckle?!
ハッ！
Why did you reveal yourself?
はぁ…　ダメだ。
Right now, your job is to stay
hidden as long as possible!
((体内にオーラをためて 一気に手のひらから吐き出す))
I'm done running and hiding.
((このパワーがあればあるほど
I'll face you.
オーラの玉を飛ばす時の 攻撃力が上がるわけ))
So...
((閉じた精孔を開放して オーラを放出する))
Let them escape.
((その時に練った オーラの総量と それを押し出す 力　速さ　タイミング
Knuckle chose to use words instead of his fists
この全てが揃わないと　狙い通りの 攻撃力は得られないわよ))
because Youpi's words had
struck a chord with him.
難しい！ 特に体内のオーラを
You're crazy.
手から押し出すってのが 難しいんだよな
You can't even call that a trade-off.
この１０日 全然　進歩してねえぜ。 やっぱ　地道にレベル２から
My answer
やってったほうが よかったんじゃね？
is no.
それもツェズゲラ次第だろ？
However...
今　思うと　あの取引も どうかなって思うしな。 「奇運アレキサンドライト」 渡しちゃったら
If you get rid of this thing,
my answer might change.
ツェズゲラ組も　あと２種類だろ。 こっちは　まだ３０種類くらい 集めなきゃいけないのに。
I'm sure this has to do with why you've
been constantly on the run.
ゲンスルーから奪っちゃえば いいじゃないの　無理やりにさ。
Removing it will make the
exchange more even.
っていうか　まず ゲンスルー倒す段取り決めなきゃ。
No... Don't do it!
で　このくらいでいいの？
Knuckle, you'd better not be stupid!
ああ。
Morel's desperate cry did not reach
Knuckle due to God's Accomplice.
これで　俺達の 「アカンパニー」４８枚。
However, it did return Meleoron to his senses.
始めるぞ 勝ちの決まった鬼ごっこをな。
Leave me here...
「アカンパニー」オン　ツェズゲラ！
You can't! You can't do that, Knuckle!
動いたぞ！ すごいスピードで近づいて来る！
Don't worry about me...
手はず通り行くぞ！
Will you waste everything we've done?
「アカンパニー」オン　マサドラへ！
have done by risking your lives!
「アカンパニー」オン　ツェズゲラ！
If Knuckle didn't act, the two of
them could still fight together.
「アカンパニー」オン ソウフラビへ！
With that in mind, the decision that
Meleoron made after leaving Morel...
「アカンパニー」オン ツェズゲラ！
Knuckle! Knuckle!
...ended up backfiring.
俺は　もうない　バリー！ 了解！
to defeat Youpi...
「アカンパニー」オン！ ソウフラビへ！
Why...
うっ…。 クソ　あと５日しかないのに…
The sight of a bloody Morel had reminded
Knuckle of Shoot, and broken him.
何か　きっかけになるような アドバイスとか　ないのかよ。 オーラが体内を流れる 感覚ってのは
Okay... I took away APR!
似てるようで　一人一人違うのよ。
Now the terms are even.
下手に私の感覚を伝えて 先入観を植えつけたら
Leave the boss alone!
逆効果になることのほうが 多いしね。
Fight me!
ハッ！
Kill me!
「アカンパニー」は残り７枚。
No way.
来ないな　諦めたか？
Hold on!
まさか　緩急をつけて 動揺させる気だろう。
Where are you going?!
「アカンパニー」がなくなったら 「リターン」だぞ。
To the King, obviously.
分かってる　アイアイと ソウフラビを交互にな。
Do you want to come with me?
向こうの様子は？
I doubt you could handle it.
聞いてみよう。 「コンタクト」オン　ゴレイヌ。
His ability isn't teleportation, is it?
ツェズゲラだ そっちは　どうだ？ サブとバラが現れた 恐らく　こっちが本物。
Then you'll have to carry the
guy in sunglasses to a doctor, or you struck this deal for nothing.
俺がカードを買いに来ると 読んでの作戦だろう。 今 あんた達を追っかけてるのは ゲンスルーと偽者だぜ。
If protecting the King was his first priority, he should have killed all three on the spot.
ツェズゲラの予想が ズバリ当たったな。
It's no big deal...
二度と同じては食わんさ。 今なら実質 あっちは　ゲンスルー１人。
You weaklings can attack me all you
want, but I'll still shake you off.
こっちは４人　チャンスだぜ。 いや　勝算は 高ければ高いほどいい。 最初の計画通り行く。
The fact that he was aware of this,
but didn't carry it out, irritated Youpi on a level that didn't
compare to his previous rage.
ハッ！
I don't need to kill you right now...
くっ…。 ゴン。 タイムアップだ　修行は終わり。
And that's all there is to it!
まだ５日あるよ！
Damn, I picked up Pouf's habit.
予定変更　奴らを倒すための 作戦が決まったんだ。 でも…　でも！ あの　えと
During this battle, Youpi had learned
how profound Nen really was.
もう少しで　できそう…　かも。
That also altered what little
sense of self he'd had before.
いや　無理 できるかどうか分からないのを 作戦に組み込むわけには いかないしな。 諦めろ。 はぁ…。 で　その作戦ってのは…。 こいつを使う。
Having learned to quarantine
his rage and stay calm, Youpi had lost his ability to
see things in simple terms.
完璧にできるようになるまでな。 「リターン」行くぞ！
They're responsible for the rage I've built up, so why don't I feel like using it on them?
「リターン」オン！　アイアイへ！
What, or who, am I supposed
to unleash this rage upon?
「アカンパニー」が切れたか いよいよ大詰めだな。
Was this a sign of maturation? Youpi wasn't sure.
１匹だけな。
However, as for Knuckle...
ボマーが　ここで プレーヤーを狩ってるのが もう広まってるみたいで 誰も来ねえよ。
I completely lost...
ツェズゲラの仲間。 かもな　よし　戻って来てくれ 今　ソウフラビにいる。
We gotta help the big guy!
ひぃ！ うっ…！
Come on, boss.
奴らは　もう　タネ切れだ。
I told you to leave me here...
奴らがゲームの外まで 追って来れば　城で返り討ち。
The two of you... can still fight.
来なければ 約束の日時まで　ただ待てばいい。
Do what you can.
完璧さ　あとはクリア後の カード３枚の選択。
He said to go whenever you want.
バッテラ氏が　どのカードが 欲しいのか聞くだけだ。
So go now!
よし　行くぞ！
I can't.
「リーブ」！
I can no longer think of him...
誰もいないぞ。
He wasn't a bad guy.
どうなってる？ 武装兵が待機してるはずだろ。 サバズシ　どこだ！ いるなら返事しろ！　サバズシ！
In that case, I no longer have... any reason to defeat him.
うるせぇな せっかく昼寝してたのによ。
The King... Knov-san!
寝てただと？ 他の連中は　どうした？
The soldiers are not important.
帰ったよ。 な…！ バッテラ直々のキャンセルだ。 仲介料と キャンセル料は　もらったが
If the King waves his baton, the soldiers
will become demons if necessary.
あんたには　一応　報告しとこうと 思って待ってたんだ。
I'll take care of Morel... Shoot is also okay.
バッテラさん 一体どういうことです？
Are you guys also coming? Wait, let me sock this baby hard.
あと少しなんですよ？ もうすぐクリアできるんです！
I received a message from
the chairman's messenger.
もういい　いいんだ…
As planned, he was able to take the
King to the appointed location.
何がいいんだ　ふざけるな！ 我々の今までの苦労は　どうなる！
If they leave now, the Royal
Guard won't make it in time.
カードは　好きにしていい。
Their job is done, and so is ours. Where's Palm?
だから　もう
We don't know yet. Okay...
私を１人にしてくれ。
What will you do? I don't know if I'll be back again.
クソっ。
You can see how bad I look...
どういうことなんだ？
Are you going or staying?
ぐあ！
We're staying. We still have a job to do.
指輪のデータが消えないからな。
You're strong...
ゴン達との約束を果たすべく 時間を稼いだツェズゲラ達
Let's go.
だが　そこに待っていたのは 予期せぬ事態だった
To look for Palm? No, we can do that later. There's something else we have to do.